[music]
Hey buddy, you look like you got a very
lot of money. Bro, bro, I don't have
money, bro. Give me your own pet. I want
to see your own pet.
Hey, so stubborn slow.
Mama,
>> where is papa. Papa is gone, dear.
>> Oh my god. I want papa.
>> It's okay.
>> Are you Amy's wife, Miss Aarin?
>> Yes, I am.
>> Your [music] rent has been over you for
months. When you want to pay it,
>> I don't get any money. It's like that.
You need to [music] move up.
>> No, no, no.
Can we sit there?
[music]
Why does our life have to be like this?
Mom, I cannot stand it anymore. I just
want that.
I'm sorry, honey. I promise we change
our [music] life. It's okay. I will find
a new daddy.
It was just a dream. But if you're real,
I cannot let my family suffer after I'm
gone.
I need to get insurance.
early the next morning.
>> How can I help you today, sir?
>> I want to protect my wife and daughter
if anything happen to me.
>> We offer you our whole life insurance
plan. Here are you with your class.
>> So now I know my family will be safe no
matter what happens. Right. Thank you.
Mama s I want to let you know that I
already have insurance.
>> Wow. Thank you papa.
>> This one way I'm planning ahead and
being responsible.
>> Thank you mama. Thank you papa.
>> The area with you plus is a life
insurance that covers both protection
and service. It covers death, natural or
accidental TPD, total and permanent
disability with coverage up to 70 or 80
years depending on the plan choosing.
You can also add optional writers such
as chronic illness, accident or medical
coverage. It provides financial
protection to family members if the
policy holder passes away. The policy
also includes savings element with cash
value with flexible premium payment
terms. The policy is also suitable for
long-term financial planning. We argue
with your class does not cover first
suicide within the first 13 months from
policy
issue. Second, death or injury due to
itself inflicted harm. Third, death
caused by participation in illegal
activities. Fourth, fraud,
misrepresentation
or non-disclosure of material facts as
well as claims arising from war, riot or
civil commotion based on the policy.
[music]
>> [music]